The Journey Into '80s Horror Continues
In Search of Darkness: Part II is a documentary,
horror film directed by David A. Weiner.
The ultimate ‘80s Horror retrospective just got BIGGER.
In Search of Darkness: Part II is a four-hour-plus sequel to the Rondo Hatton-nominated In Search of Darkness, adding 15 new
interviewees and 40+ returning favorites for the biggest and most comprehensive ‘80s Horror documentary cast ever assembled.
Self, played by Nancy Allen.
Self, played by Tom Atkins.
Self, played by Doug Bradley.
Self, played by John Bloom.
Self, played by Clancy Brown.
Self, played by Lori Cardille.
In Search of Darkness: Part II is a 2020 documentary
film written and directed by David A.
It is a sequel  to Weiner's 2019 documentary In Search of Darkness.
Unlike the first documentary, which featured more mainstream films, Part II focuses on
more obscure movies and features over four hours of new interviews.
For Part II, I definitely made a very concerted effort to go on an international scope and do a lot of the B-sides and straight-to-video
deep cuts...There’s something special about horror films, where the fans will really love them like their own homely child.
They circle the wagons around their favorites and
defend them ‘till their dying breath.
We all love these films for different reasons and we all acknowledge that while The Shining
might be the cream of the crop, Chopping Mall still has a place in our hearts.
The documentary premiered on Shudder on April 26, 2021.
The tone is dark.